

# OKORO CHIMEZIE BRIGHT

Full-Stack Web Developer

# **PROFILE**

I'm a full-stack web developer with over 4 years' experience in software development.

Experienced in meeting clients to collect software requirements, leading teams, excellent communication skills with problem solving skills, supporting engineers and software architecture.

Agile or water-fall development practice with html5, css3,

JavaScript and cross-browser compatibility.

# CONTACT

PHONE:

+841252181203 or 0394755263

WEBSITE:

https://okorochimezieportfolio1.netlify.app/

GITHUB:

https://github.com/mezieb

FMAII:

Okorobright13@gmail.com

CURRENT LOCATION: Hanoi, Vietnam.

## **HOBBIES**

- Reading
- Listening to music
- Swimming
- Meeting people

### **EDUCATION**

### University of Nigeria Nuskka, UNN.

2007 - 2011

Mathematics (B.Sc./Ed).

### FPT University, Hanoi, Vietnam.

2015 - 2017

Software Engineering (M, SE). Area of specialization data analytic.

### Industrial training courses.

Udemy certification 2021

Course: The Complete 2021 Web Development Bootcamp.

Instructors: Dr Angela Yu.

Certificate no: UC-72bd0c3a-79c0-487d-99fa-c64d1b8efc26

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Company: IGHOLINK SYSTEMS TECHOLOGIES NIGERIA

2011-2014

ROLE: Data Analyst RESPONSIBILITY:

- 1. to determine the type of data that will be analyzed.
- 2. Information gathering
- 3. Clean the data before analyzing it with tools like python or r
- 4. Examine the data
- 5. Presentation of my findings.

### Company: kpibsc Vietnam

2016-2019

ROLE: Foreign sales representative

**RESPONSIBILITY:** 

- 1. Meeting foreign clients to collect software requirements.
- 2. Pitching the software product to foreign clients.
- 3. Organizing professional English classes for team members.
- 4. Team leader in balancing communication to the developer team and foreign clients.

Project type: key performance indicator balance score card management tools.

Project link: https://kpibsc.com/

# Freelancer Web Developer

2019-till date

Client: spago Vietnam

Project type: spa management tools Project link: <a href="https://www.spago.vn/">https://www.spago.vn/</a>

Role: frontend developer

RESPONSIBLILTY: Template builder with html,css,javascript from figma design with a given specifications like colors,fonts,images,logo etc.

I help you design your ideal website from simple to complex, with a business solution that suit your business needs in phases.

Feel free to contact me and let's do it together.

https://okorochimezie-portfolio1.netlify.app/

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- 1: HTML5
- 2: CSS3
- 3: JAVASCRIPT , TYPESCRIT

4: REACT JS

5: BOOTSTRAP

6: GITHUB

7:PYTHON

8:FRAMEWORK – NEXTJS DJANGO,NODE JS

9:DATABASES – POSTGRESS , MYSQL